<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Businesses on 42th openheart</title>
    <link>https://www.openheart.icu/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Businesses on 42th openheart</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>ALL RIGHTS RESERVED KRIS NIE</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 23:29:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.openheart.icu/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Configure &amp; Price &amp; Quote</title>
      <link>https://www.openheart.icu/business/configure-price-quote/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 23:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.openheart.icu/business/configure-price-quote/</guid>
      <description>Configure &amp;amp; Price &amp;amp; Quote Visual configuration Leverage a powerful, dynamic, and visually interactive experience to bring product options and final product configurations to life.
 3D interactive model creation 2D parametric drawing generation 3D CAD assemblies and shop drawings creation Augmented reality experience  Innovative quoting and ordering Capture interest and knowledge about your highly variable products or systems once, and then share with customers and selling channels to make the selection and purchase process intuitive and error-free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Orders</title>
      <link>https://www.openheart.icu/business/customer-orders/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 23:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.openheart.icu/business/customer-orders/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s the CO A customer order is a formal order from the customer which provides details of the amount and due date for a customer’s requirement of products.
It is a written document specifying the orders made by the customer. It states the amount of money to be paid, the due date on which the money can be expected, and the quantity of the product delivered.
(It is mainly used in business to help customers get their products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inventory</title>
      <link>https://www.openheart.icu/business/inventory/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 23:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.openheart.icu/business/inventory/</guid>
      <description>Counting Physical Inventory Counting
Cycle Counting
 Container Containerization: 集装箱化
 Transfer order processing The following table displays the steps for using a transfer order.
The following graphic displays the transfer inventory flow.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Orders</title>
      <link>https://www.openheart.icu/business/job-orders/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 23:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.openheart.icu/business/job-orders/</guid>
      <description>Backflushing Automatic deduction of material or components Backflushing is a method of updating inventory records at a defined point in the manufacturing process, called the deduct point.
倒冲就是为了在保证生产的效率，对于生产过程中价值较低、使用频繁、数量较大的物料（比如螺丝、螺帽各种油、漆液体类原材料）根据BOM（物料清单）中设置的标准消耗量在对生产订单报工时自动进行物料消耗的一种方法，比如生产一个产品A，需要使用2个原材料A1，在对产品A报工时产生为100，系统就自动消耗200个A1到生产订单，至于系统标准消耗的量和实际消耗量之间的差异，则通过实际盘点实现，通常需要设置车间线边库专门核算和管理倒冲的物料，也便于在月底对线边库盘点差异，差异的处理则根据实际情况分析是否需调整标准消耗量还是要加强车间材料管理降低损耗率等。
 To use backflushing, you must set up the backflushing location on the Inventory Parameters form. You cannot perform backflushing operations on items from consignment warehouse locations. If you have material in a vendor consignment warehouse when you perform a backflush, the system will check that warehouse for the required material.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Material Planning</title>
      <link>https://www.openheart.icu/business/material-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 23:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.openheart.icu/business/material-planning/</guid>
      <description>Bill of Materials  Low Level Code The low-level code represents the lowest level of the item in any current, job, or production schedule bill of material (BOM). A low-level code of 0 indicates that the item is an end item (finished good) and is not a subcomponent of another item. A low-level code greater than zero indicates that the item is a component of another item. The system supports up to 20 levels of low-level coding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Material Requirements Planning</title>
      <link>https://www.openheart.icu/business/material-requirements-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 23:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.openheart.icu/business/material-requirements-planning/</guid>
      <description>Prior to MRP  Reorder point (ROP) Reorder-quantity (ROQ) type methods like EOQ (economic order quantity)  MRP Material Requirements Planning was computerized by the aero engine makers Rolls Royce and General Electric in the early 1950s but not commercialized by them. It was then &amp;lsquo;reinvented&amp;rsquo; to supply the Polaris program and then, in 1964, as a response to the Toyota Manufacturing Program(TPS), Joseph Orlicky developed material requirements planning (MRP). The first company to use MRP was Black &amp;amp; Decker in 1964, with Dick Alban as project leader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purchase Orders</title>
      <link>https://www.openheart.icu/business/purchase-orders/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 23:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.openheart.icu/business/purchase-orders/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s the PO While purchase order refers to an outgoing order for the purchase of goods or services, the term sales order is used in the instance that the order is received on the sales side (incoming).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market-Based Management</title>
      <link>https://www.openheart.icu/business/market-based-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 14:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.openheart.icu/business/market-based-management/</guid>
      <description>Business Foundations Key Vision Role of business in Society Value Creation Virtuous Cycles of Mutual Benefit Head Wind &amp;amp; Heal Wind Strategic Planning Tools MBM Framework Angela Dou Introduce their Invista NYLON business.
Dacron &amp;amp; Cordura &amp;amp; Molex will use their nylon 66.
5 Dimensions Vision(愿景)  合伙人的共同愿景 设定目标 重要的是人，而非事 资源优化 观点 危机四伏的商业世界  Virtus &amp;amp; Talents(品德与才能)  践行指导原则 言出必行 招贤纳士 量身定制 人才规划 绩效发展 职业发展  Knowledge Processes(知识流程)  自发性知识分享 外部网络 咨询师 信息创造价值 衡量指标 边际分析 对标管理 利润中心 挑战流程 知识与价值创造  Decision Rights: Property rights inside the organization(决策权：组织内部的产权问题)  决策权与决策权的优化、上移和下放 决策框架 决策陷阱 劳动分工 角色、职责和要求（RREs）  Incentives: Motivating the right behavior(激励：鼓励合理行为)  激励员工追求自我实现 激励机制和与外部协调的激励机制 不满足是一种动力 激励的协调和统一 激励与失败 边际贡献  Evaluating What Matters Key Financial Metrics NIAT 税后净利润</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Country&#39;s Economy</title>
      <link>https://www.openheart.icu/business/our-countrys-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 14:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.openheart.icu/business/our-countrys-economy/</guid>
      <description>微观机制 地方政权与事务 政府治理 中央与地方政府 中国宪法规定，中华人民共和国的行政区域划分如下：
　（一）全国分为省、自治区、直辖市；
　（二）省、自治区分为自治州、县、自治县、市；
　（三）县、自治县分为乡、民族乡、镇。
目前中国有34个省级行政区，包括23个省、5个自治区、4个直辖市、2个特别行政区。在历史上和习惯上，各省级行政区都有简称。截止2022年3月24日，如下图：
多重领导 中央政府的主要部委，除外交部等个别例外，在各级政府中均有对应部门，比如中央政府有财政部，省政府有财政厅，市县政府有财政局等。让领导更复杂的是，各个部门又以行政区域为界，大多数地方部门都同时接受行政区域上级部门的双重领导。比如县教育局，既要接受市教育局的指导，又要服从县委、县政府的领导。通常情况下，上级部门与下级部门之间是业务关系，行政区域内才是领导关系，因为地方党委和政府可以决定人事任免。
上级领导与协调  制度设计的一大任务就是要避免把过多决策推给上级，减轻上级负担，提高决策效率，所以体制内简化决策流程的原则之一，就是尽量在能达成共识的最低层级上解决问题。
 官僚主义  官员必须学习和贯彻统一的意识形态；官员由上级人名；地方主官需要在多地轮换任职。（这三条，在维持大一统的前提下，让中央与地方的人事制度更加平衡。）
  在任何体制下，权力运作都受到两种约束：做事能力及做事的意愿。前者取决于掌握的资源，后者取决于各方的积极性和主动性。
 外部性与规模经济 外部性 外部性（Externality）是指个体经济单位的行为对社会或者其他个人部门造成了影响（例如环境污染）却没有承担相应的义务或获得回报，亦称外部成本、外部效应或溢出效应。这种外部效应有时产生有利影响（教育和安全提高社会生产力），有时会产生不利影响（污染和犯罪降低社会生产力）。我们可以按照外部效应产生的影响不同，把外部效应分为外部经济和外部不经济。
 若行政区域太小而导致影响外溢、需要上级协调的事情过多，本级政府也就失去了存在的意义。反过来讲，行政区划也限定了地方可调配的资源，下至了其政策的影响范围。
 规模经济  按照经典经济学的看法，政府的核心职能就是提供公共物品和公共服务，比如国防和公园。
 大规模生产导致的经济效益简称**规模经济**（Economies of scale)，是指在一定的产量范围内，随着产量的增加，平均成本不断降低的事实。规模经济是由于一定的产量范围内，固定成本可以认为变化不大，那么新增的产品就可以分担更多的固定成本，从而使总成本下降。
典型就是家庭生活支出，衣食住行中，分散到家庭中每个人中，成本会降低，无法分散成本是单身的缺点之一。
出自汉密尔顿之手的《联邦在政府经济方面的优越性》（ADVANTAGE OF THE UNION IN RESPECT TO ECONOMY IN GOVERNMENT）被收录在《联邦党人文集》中，并编号13。讲一个大政府比13个小政府更省钱的道理，也就是规模经济。
行政区域划分取决于公共服务性质、内容、效果。影响公共服务效果的因素有：
 人口密度：“民稠则减，稀则旷”（《汉书 · 百官公卿表》） 地理条件：“然天下初定，权置州郡颇多，太宗元年，始命并省，又因山川形便，分天下为十道”（《新唐书 · 地理志》） 语言文化差异：可参考《中国语言地图集》。  当然，这些都只是勾勒了一个大致框架，无法涵盖所有复杂情况：
 人工密集变化频繁，但行政区域的调整缓慢得多。部分人口流入地可以”撤县建区“来扩展城市，人口流出地很少裁撤行政单位，一般只是合并一些公共设施来降低成本，比如撤并农村中小学。 为了政治稳定需求，人为打破自然边界，不以天险为界来划分行政区域，防止地方势力依天险制造分裂。 方言与文化区域经常被行政区域割裂。比如客家话虽然是主要方言，但整个客家话大区被江西、福建、广东三省分割；苏南、苏北之分；苏州、无锡、常州本和浙江一样同属吴语区，却与讲江淮官话的苏北一道被划入了江苏省。  行政交界地区  省会（除南京和西宁）无一临近边界，限制了边界地区获取公共资源。 部分省边界地理复杂，不利于经济发展。 方言与主流不通，在本省之内与主流文化隔阂，而与邻省同文化区域又被行政边界割裂，不利于经济发展。比如江西、福建、广东交界处的客家话区，与三省主流的赣语、闽语、粤语都不同；安徽北部，基本属于河南、山东一脉的中原官话区，与省内主流的江淮官话不同。 环境污染治理问题，尤其是跨省的大江大河大湖，比如黄河、淮河、太湖等流域的污染。这是典型的外部性问题。 地方保护主义和市场分割现象，尤其在生产要素市场上，用地指标和户籍制度对土地和人口流动影响很大。  区域性调整  加强县的独立性和自主性，弱化其与市区的联系。 扩张城市，撤县设区。1983~2021年，共有190个县或县级市被撤。比如北京市原来就8个区，现在是16个，后来的8个都是由县改区，如通州区（原通县）和房山区（原房山县）；上海现有16个市辖区，青浦、奉贤、松江、金山等区也都是撤县设区改革的结果。  复杂信息 山高皇帝远。哈哈，穷乡僻壤出刁民，异曲同工！</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principles Of Economics</title>
      <link>https://www.openheart.icu/business/principles-of-economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 18:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.openheart.icu/business/principles-of-economics/</guid>
      <description>Then Principles of Economics.  &amp;hellip;It(society) must decide who will eat caviar and who will eat potatoes. It must decide who will drive a Ferrari and who will take the bus&amp;hellip;Scarcity means that society has limited resources and therefore cannot produce all the goods and services people wish to have&amp;hellip;
 经济学就是研究社会如何管理这些稀缺资源。
People Face Trade-Offs 权衡取舍（Trade-Offs）。简单明了，每个人做每件事都是在作取舍。One classic trade-off is between “guns and butter.” 社会的支出更多地用于保卫外国入侵的国防（大炮），那就用于提高国内生活水平的消费品（黄油）上的支出就少了。
程序员的职业发展也是类似取舍，”一“型、”T“型、”I“型？
社会面临的另一种权衡取舍是在效率（Efficiency）和平等（Equality）之间。效率代表蛋糕的大小，平等则指如何分割这块蛋糕。
The Cost of Something Is What You Give Up to Get It 和原则一相辅相成，薛兆丰在经济学讲义中也提到了，成本就是放弃了的最大代价（Cost is the best opportunity foregone）。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economics &amp; Finance &amp; Management</title>
      <link>https://www.openheart.icu/business/economics-finance-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 23:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.openheart.icu/business/economics-finance-management/</guid>
      <description>如何区分并界定经济学、金融学与管理学？
这24份期刊涵盖了6大领域：会计(Accounting)、金融(Finance)、IS(Information System)、营销(Marketing)、运营(Operation)和管理(Management)，除了Management Science是一份集合刊物，其他各份刊物都能对号入座
Economics 经济学是针对人类经济活动、经济关系以及经济规律的社会科学，所谓经济活动，是指将有限或者稀缺资源进行合理配置的行为。
  微观经济
  宏观经济
  Finance 金融学是将“货币资金”视作这个“有限或者稀缺资源”来进行深入研究，是经济学在货币领域的深化和细化。通俗讲，是研究怎么赚钱，通过什么方式赚钱的学科，研究个人、组织和公司等在一段时间内如何有效地筹集，分配和利用资金，是研究资金融通的学科。金融的具体内容有货币、证券、银行、保险、资本市场、衍生证券、投资理财等等。
Management 财务会计属于管理学。
The Logics of Management 管理逻辑学
Reference  商学、经济学、金融学与管理学有哪些相似与不同之处，如何具体区分？  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work Review</title>
      <link>https://www.openheart.icu/business/work-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.openheart.icu/business/work-review/</guid>
      <description>Measures KPI key performance indicator
OKR Objectives and key results
OKR.com
RRE 360 Pronounce it &amp;lsquo;Three-Sixty&amp;rsquo;.
How to increase efficiency Pomodoro Technique  Problem Solving Process Define the Problem Mostly, we can not figure out the situation: what&amp;rsquo;s the problem?
It will impact our solution. Whatever underestimate or overestimate. (Generally, we will think our solution as a line, from start to finish. But it may be a curve or cycle. So it&amp;rsquo;ll take π time to resolve it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
